This is where it starts and it just
shows the breadth and the depth of
technology that is uh here in Taiwan.
This is the epicenter of the world's
computing industry. Did I do something
wrong? I looked like a kid in a room of
adults. I noticed this beautiful girl in
the class. Listen. And I went up to her.
I used my superpowers and so I just told
her, you know, would you like to see my
homework? Where's your watch? I don't
wear a watch.
Cut it out. Stop it. I have something
for you.
Fantastic. Wow. These are all my
favorites. Oh my gosh. Don't embarrass
me.
[Music]
I remember the last time when we had our
HTD 23 together. We rode in with a, you
know, a Beauty and the Beast, you know,
SUV. Do you remember Beauty and the
Beast?
The car, the car, the car. And that car,
I have to give you uh uh let you know a
good news about it, has been chosen by
Mitsubishi to be become their car. Wow.
And that car will be uh running on the
road
uh roughly about a year from now. Okay.
Okay. With the luck you bring. That's
awesome.
And you know in this second half of the
keynote what I would like to do is to
ask you questions and let you answer.
Okay. Okay. So you know it doesn't
matter what you ask my answer always the
same.
You know I hope you know I ask you know
actually I collect a lot of questions
from the industries and from people who
care about you.
and compile them into three category of
questions. Right? Number one is business
related. Do you want me to start with
the business related stuff? If we start
with business related, I will go so long
and then there we'll end with just
business related. So let's start with
business
related. I'm afraid to hear about the
other two the other keeping keeping
under control. Okay. But it's not the
question that you thought about the
business. It's not about
Nvidia chips or you know uh system
business. It's about you know the tin
Taiwan. The very first question what is
tin Taiwan from your point of view?
Well uh Taiwan is
uh is
where our most important partners are.
We've been coming here for 30 years.
Yeah. and and uh somebody did a count.
We have 350 partners here. 350 350
um of course of course um I I don't know
them all but apparently either directly
or indirectly we work with some 350
companies and you know that the
technology supply chain is incredibly
deep here right and it's much more
complicated than people think. uh every
you know as you I made a movie the other
day that I showed yesterday and it just
shows the breadth and the depth of
technology that is uh here in Taiwan and
so as a as a as a computing company this
is the epicenter of the world's
computing industry this is where it
starts and everything from the chips of
course to the systems and now
increasingly increasingly
uh the pioneering work that is being
done in the automation of robotic
factories and building robots. You know,
you you know very well this this is um
this one of the largest electronic
manufacturing regions in the world. Yes.
And not only is it the largest, it's the
most advanced. And the things that we
build here are incredibly complicated.
Now, you and I were talking about
building GB200 servers. It has 1.2
million components. It weighs almost 2
lbs. Completely liquid cooled. Each rack
is a couple two three million dollars.
Uh all these numbers
and and numbers. Yeah. And so they're
not that hard
[Laughter]
numbers. And just so you know, I rounded
them all. It's 1.8 tons. It's 1.12
million parts. Yeah. Yeah. So I round it
up for your benefit. and and um uh so so
anyways the technology is incredibly
complicated in order to build one of
those grace black wall racks uh how many
companies were involved and how much
robotics technology is actually involved
you know so if you look at look just
look at the work that we've done uh in
the last two years since you and I uh
were on stage together starting to talk
about AI and robotics since
then Foxcon is using Nvidia uh
Metropolis
for smart cities. Nvidia Metropolis for
smart factories. Nvidia Isaac Groot for
robotics. Nvidia Drive for autonomous
vehicles. Uh Nvidia Omniverse as the
digital twin operating system for all of
that.
And yesterday we
announced that we're going to build an
AI factory, right, for you to use, for
me to use, and for Taiwan, the entire
ecosystem to use. Yes. Yeah. And so, so
now Foxcon is going to be uh a
worldclass uh regional cloud provider,
AI cloud provider. And so, so look at
the breadth of work that we do together
now. Uh it covers literally every uh not
to mention uh for for uh uh
manufacturing uh inspection agents with
computer vision and vision understanding
and so everything from a agents to
robots robots to you know robots with
wheels, robots that are orchestrating
robots to build robots you know and so
this is this is um I've seen that this
is robots building robots. Yeah, this is
in person. This is literally Foxcon.
This is Foxcon, you know, one of the
most advanced technology companies in
the world. You just happen to apply
technology to manufacturing. You know,
we apply technology for technology sake.
You apply the technology to apply for
manufacturing. And so it can't it can't
uh you know, we shouldn't be we
shouldn't be surprised. Uh but everybody
should be deeply impressed by the
technology of Foxcon. Thank you very
much. Yeah. And so did you notice? I
just want to demonstrate something. It
didn't matter what he asked.
No, I asked only one question and that
question. That's where Go ahead and ask
about my jacket.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I just want
to demonstrate something. Okay. Okay.
I'm not going to ask about jacket. Okay.
No, I just want to demonstrate it
doesn't matter what you ask, you'll
answer the same thing. Okay. I see.
Because from there I was going to talk
about Omniverse and robotics.
Great salesperson. Anyway, you know the
my next question is have you heard about
tea?
From who?
Tea. Is it
association? Taiwan
uh electronics and electrical
manufacturers association. Did I do
something wrong? No. Oh, there's
something he doesn't know. I was just
made the chairman of tea. Tea. Well,
congratulations.
[Music]
Teima. Congratulations. Did you do
something wrong?
I hope I hope no. But anyway, it's a
largest uh association uh in Taiwan with
uh more than 3,000 members and accounts
for over 50% of export value of Taiwan.
Okay. Aggregate number of workers in
Taiwan. Foxcon represented 40% of
export.
Okay. 30 37%.
because our business model we're
worldwide. So, you know, the the the
revenue you know counted in Taiwan is
only about half. Okay.
So, PEA is the um the association. I
think most of the members are you know
most of your suppliers are members of
tea. Okay. Now with this rapid changing
AI
industry, what advices do you have for
your
suppliers in the team uh as a team
member? Mhm. Any advices for them? Um
yeah, I do. I I will come to me in just
a second. Um but I'm just going to have
to
start. I do. So let let me make an
observation. Let me make an observation.
uh in fact vast majority of the
industrial the industries
uh the company's focus on
industries has largely
uh been left behind as during the
software revolution and the reason for
that is because you're obviously
industrial because you understand
meatronics you understand mechanicals
you understand chemicals you understand
the deep physics part the sciences part
of industry that industry
was was uh formed out of the last
industrial revolution and Taiwan is is
excellent in those industries. But when
software came, I was a brand new skill
and those skills were quite unusual and
quite unnatural for for uh these
companies. Number one, number two, first
observation. The second observation is
that when AI started 10 years ago, uh it
was very interesting but not very
useful.
not very useful for the industrial
companies. And the reason for that is
because the AI understands English, but
it doesn't understand physics, which is
what you need. Everything that you do
needs physical understanding, physical
intelligence. Mhm. You know, when I roll
a ball underneath a car, my dog knows to
either go underneath a car or go around
the car. But the AI thinks the ball has
disappeared out of this universe. Mhm.
Mhm. And so, uh, we need to under we
need to have physical common sense. Now,
we're developing both of those things.
Now, why is AI so great? The reason for
that is because you teach an AI. You
don't have to program an
AI. Software programming skills is no
longer as vital as it was before. You
have an opportunity to leap the software
chasm and go directly to AI. In fact, I
can prove it to
you. Everybody is a software programmer.
Now, the definition of a software
programmer is somebody who programs a
computer to do something. Right? That's
a software programmer. Give me an
example of somebody who can't tell
ChatGpt to do something. And if you
don't know how to even tell ChatGpt to
do something, you say, "Chat GPT, teach
me how to teach you how to do
something." Yeah. Isn't that right? And
Chad GPD writes a very nice prompt and
say, "Try this." And I say,
"Okay, isn't that right?" Incredible.
So, this computer is now intelligent and
intelligent systems are easier to use.
And now you have an intelligent system
that's easier to use. It understands the
laws of physics. We combined all of that
into
omniverse. See, you see how I came back
again.
It came all the way back into omniverse
which you are using as a digital twin.
Isn't that right? And within the digital
twin within the digital twin you could
design your plants, you could operate
your plants, you could simulate your
plants and plan everything before you
operate green field or brownfield.
Exactly. Isn't that right? And so all of
a sudden every company in tea, every
company in tea is now a technology
company and has to be right has to be a
technology company. It doesn't matter
what you ask me.
Okay. Now if I switch to ask a one track
mind personal related questions it's
going to come right back to tea.
Okay, I think for tea uh I think they uh
heard it and they will have to keep up
with the AI and uh transform themselves
to have more and more software
capabilities. Yeah. Right. And in fact,
you know, look, every company needs to
do what Foxcon did. When you and I first
talked about AI, you didn't talk about
AI and read about AI and kept thinking
about AI. You just started working on
AI.
just get to it. You know, of course, the
technology two years ago is not as
advanced as it is today. Right. Right.
But you knew that. You knew that it was
going to get better. You knew that
technology was going to get better all
of course it does. It's getting better
at a million times every 10 years. A
million times every 10 years. It's like
changing every day. And it is. AI is
changing every single day. And so, but
you engage it today with an expectation
that these challenges that you're
experiencing are going to get solved
almost by itself. But you've got to get
engaged right away. You've everybody has
to develop develop a system. We have a
system available to you. You bring it to
your company and and you know, Foxcon
and I will build it for you. The all the
software is capable available for you.
We're already integrated into all of
your software developers whether it's
Cadence or Seammens or right the so or
out of desk or whoever it is. We're
already working with all of your
software developers. Omniverse is
integrated into all of that. Nemo is
integrated into all of that. And so you
could start trying AI and it's amazing
what you've produced in just the last
couple years. The demos you showed me,
you know, your factories are
basically complete digital twins and
they look so real. Yes. They look so
real robots working inside it.
Incredible. So in the past we have
physical factories. Then we use
omniverse to create digital twins.
That's right. And then we realized we
need AI factories to support both of
them. That's right. To make it more and
more
powerful. And all these changes evolve
so fast. And the reason why it's
evolving so fast is all because that
man
you create the chips learning so fast
and advancing so fast every year.
And my qu my next question for you do
you see any limit in terms of a hardware
speed you know for the AI remember
Moore's law ended Mo's law ended because
we're at the limits of
physics and so the cost of the
transistors going up as it should the
energy efficiency
um of the transistors and the processors
are not going up very past
understandably and so we have to try
different skills and different
techniques and so we're developing
multi-chip packages 3D packages one way
to do that the other way to do that of
course is this incredible invention
called MVL link where we connect all of
these chips together into one giant chip
you know the size of the wafer is
probably like this and so all of these
chips are working together as one used
advanced mechanical systems and liquid
cooling systems to compress the systems
into liquid one giant rack but very
importantly software you know our
architecture and the algorithms that
we're developing on top of it allows us
to re reformulate the AI models
reformulate how the work is distributed
across these supercomputers the
networking of course is a big big
challenge and a and a big opportunity
instead of passing information back and
forth we could do in network in fabric
reduction yeah and So uh you know we all
send our our answer together for us to
uh combine all the answers but why don't
we just send it to the network the
network combines the answers and already
sends it back to us so we don't have to
receive it so we reduce the amount of
traffic like practically in half and so
all of these clever ideas combined has
allowed us to improve AI performance
tremendously you know people say it's
about you know I don't know 2x every six
months. I actually think it's probably
working faster than 2x every six months
at this point. You know, it's probably
like 2x every 3 months. The combination
of all these things, I call it full
stack, but basically you're innovating
chips, innovating systems, in innovating
at the data center, innovating the
operating system of the data center and
innovating the model all at the same
time. So from what you see so far, the
only the sky is the limit.
only only the sky's is the limit and and
this is the really amazing thing young
so there's the there's the computer
industry that was
created and remember um the first time I
realized this was going to be an
industry like the computer industry was
going to be was when Bill Gates in one
of his interviews and he was he was so
young it was 1984
1984 maybe 1985 I heard an interview
where he said that Microsoft oft is not
a maker of word processors or
spreadsheets. It's a it's a manufacturer
of software. And at the time I heard
it's a manufacturer of software. What
does that mean? Software is so easy to
manufacture. You write one copy and you
the rest of it is duplicated. Okay. The
rest of it is free. And so how would you
create an industry where everything that
you produce is free? Well, of course, he
invented licensing. Yeah. And so yeah, I
I didn't realize what he had in mind was
a whole bunch of lawyers and and um uh
but but more importantly what he meant
was there's a methodology there's a
production methodology associated with
software and look at all the software
they produce today. It was a visionary
idea and now it's a trillion dollar
industry. Well, our industry remember AI
is a great technology, but AI is also an
industry in itself. Just as software,
you know, you got spreadsheets and word,
but the collectively software is an
industry in itself. AI is going to be an
industry. However, the AI is going to be
produced by factories.
And so now you just have to think how
large is the automation agents and
robots industries that we'll we'll
support and every one of those agents
and robots will need factories to
produce the tokens for them at all
times. You know I think I think that
we've unquestionably discovered invented
created a new multi- trillion dollar
industry which is the reason why
everybody's so excited about it.
Excellent. Excellent. Okay. So, you
know, the time is running short. I'm
trying I have so many other questions as
much as I can to exhaust all of the
time. Thank you. Thank you. Then I'm
going to skip some of the technology
related questions. I'm going to go to
the personal question. I hope you will
not be
offended. Okay, let's take a technology
question.
You know, in China, everybody knows all
my favorite restaurants in Taiwan
anyway. No, no, no. It's not that.
Everybody knows where I'm going to be
this afternoon. It's not that. You know,
for in there's a old Chinese saying that
every successful man stands a terrific
woman. I'm not going to ask you who that
woman
is. But I want to ask you, you know, do
you want I hope it's the same one I have
in mind.
So, do you want say something to her?
openly
openly. I say some I say the same thing
to her every day. Love you,
honey. And and so anyways, I met her
when I was 17 years old and she was she
was she had just turned 19. And um and
so so I I dated an older woman for most
of most of my life. What part what part
of the uh states you met her? Oregon.
Oregon. Yeah. We were lab partners in
electrical engineering. Oh, lab partner.
There were Okay. So, so imagine the
odds. Imagine how smart you have to be
to achieve this. Okay. So, there are 250
students in electrical engineering
fundamentals. There were only three
girls. I was
also so statistically
impossible. Not only that, it is very
clear who's the youngest person in
class. I was 128 pounds going to
college. I graduated at 132 lbs or
something like that. Okay, I was 128
pounds. And so I was definitely I looked
like a kid when in a room of adults. And
so I just went up to her and uh I
noticed I noticed this beautiful
beautiful girl in the class. Listen,
listen. And I went up to her and I I I
used my superpowers.
superpower because I knew that I knew
just looking around at the audience who
everybody knows what my skills are. And
so I just told her, you know, would you
like to see my homework
[Laughter]
because I those are my superpowers.
The homework everybody has superpowers.
And so so I also told her that that uh I
don't know what grades you have probably
very good. However, if you study with me
every Sunday, I promise you, you'll get
straight
A's. Every Sunday. And so I had a date
every Sunday. Oh, I see. I see. Very
smart. Yes. Yes. Yeah. That tells us the
reason why he is so successful starts
from age
17. Okay. Not just now.
Okay. Okay, my last question for you is
that
you know everybody is curious about your
jacket, but I'm not. You know, recently
your watch is becoming very popular.
I don't I don't know. You don't? No.
Where is your watch? I don't wear a
watch.
But on the news, is that fake news?
Yeah, it's fake news.
Oh, really? Oh, that's a fake news. Then
I had to tell my wife, "No, that's a
fake news. I'm not going to buy you a
watch at that price."
Okay, that's a fake news. That's it. No,
no, that's fake news. I don't wear a
watch.
I see. I don't care about the time. I
Right now is all that I don't care
about. That's why I don't wear a watch.
I'm 100% right here. Okay.
He really confused
me. Is that watch news a fake a fake
news? It's probably a fake watch.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Yeah, we're very happy to have you here
and uh you know through the conversation
we know the other side of uh Jensen and
hopefully it will help you you know to
uh to know Jensen more besides his chips
and his success in his business. Well,
my chips are pretty
good and don't let me and but but if I
could say if I could say young um I am
delighted by our partnership. Uh
obviously we're manufacturing the most
advanced computers the world's ever seen
and ever known and and uh during our
meeting yesterday uh one of your leaders
said uh no one has ever manufactured
systems this complicated but very
importantly no one has ever manufactured
supercomputers at this rate. Yes, most
of the time you plan a supercomput for
three years and you build one. We're
cranking it out every hour. And so the
idea that we're doing this at the scale
that we're talking about is
extraordinary. But that's that's the
work that we do together for my benefit.
The thing that I'm really excited is
that you then use this incredible AI
technology to revolutionize transform
Foxcon and also to make it available for
all of the Taiwan researchers and
students and other startups and other
and all the industries. I think it's
it's a great example that you're
showing. It's great that you're
revolutionizing your own company with
technology. Uh you were amazing
technology company already before. Now
you extraordinary technology company and
then everything that you do for Taiwan.
So, I'm very very grateful. Thank you.
Thank you very much, J. Thank you for
your Thank you, everybody. Thank you.
Bye. Bye.
Hey, Rick. Hey, J. See you.
No, the real star is here. Oh, cut it
out. Stop it.
Well, Jensen, I I tell
you number one, I truly appreciate and
uh all the collaboration we have here,
automotive, IoT, supercomputer, cloud,
AS6. I also truly enjoy your talk back
in March and yesterday. And they're very
different by the
way. They're all very so so powerful.
so unrehearsed.
I think that's what he's trying to say.
No, no, no, no, no. I mean, you can
never beat him.
But I mean,
uh, all so strikes me all the time. I I
told my people all the time, I don't
know how you manage so many
things in one year. You have so many new
things. So products, hardware,
software, subsystem
It's easy. Oh, no. Tell tell us. Tell
us. Would you? You just tell people what
you want and it
happens. I think we have people from
Nvidia here, right? Hey, where are you
guys? I don't I don't have to do it. I
just have to have it be
done. Do our people understand
that? Well, Rick, you know, listen, I
love our partnership. The fact of the
matter is I bet most of the people in
this audience do not know the scale of
AI infrastructure media tech has. And
the reason for that is because they're
doing advanced research in AI,
developing AI models, creating all this
amazing technology that you could use in
consumer electronics, right? Home
electronics, all of the home theater
technology and the super res technology
and audio technology for your cars. And
you you're you're turning a car into a
home theater. And so that's that's
number one is all of the AI work that we
do together and and uh the investment
that you make and a dedication you have
to AI infrastructures. A lot of great AI
researchers at
MediaTek. You know that right?
Okay.
Yes. Exactly. That's number one. Number
two, the work that we do in the
automotive ind industry together and and
I'm really delighted by that and I I
really do hope that the the incredible
multimedia technology you put into home
theaters around the world for us and can
go into cars and then we work in uh of
course uh this revolutionary product we
called DJX Spark. Now the CPU and the
GPU are both state-of-the-art but what's
amazing is that you saw it they abut
together using this MVL link. Yes. In
fact that project inspired us to think
of MVLink fusion.
The fact of the matter is we were able
to work together in creating this chip
and the chip is state-of-the-art. It
came up and running in the first day.
It's running at full speed. The
performance is incredible
and you know it's going to be a miracle
when we go to production. People are
going to be shocked at what it can do.
Now remember a 200 million parameter
model runs on this thing. And 200
million parameters if you connect two of
these DJX sparks together it's 400
because it's multiplied by two. And it's
incredible. And so so I think that that
um the the big idea is this. Look, the
personal computer's here. Uh mobile
devices are here. We already have our
personal devices. But in the world of AI
native applications, the only way to
enjoy AI is connected to the cloud.
There is no way to have well rich AI,
you know, 200 million parameter AI,
large language models, generative models
that are fairly significant. The only
way to do that is in the cloud. So we we
decided that we should build a
personal device, a personal computer for
the AI first world. And that's what DGX
Park is. If you're a developer, it
connects to you just like you connect to
the cloud. Uh when you're done
developing, you could host it and you
know all of your applications just like
that as if it's in the cloud. And so
every AI developer is going to want one
of these. every student researcher 30
million of them around the world. We're
going to produce, you know, DJX Sparks
in high volume, which is the reason why
we needed so many part, we got so many
people excited about it that all of the
world's OEMs are going to be part of the
distribution channels. They're all going
to be doing differentiated versions of
it, taking it to market. And so we have
DJX Spark. But the idea, the big idea um
is uh MVLink Fusion. You know as you
know AI is a very different computing
model whereas hypers scale are few
applications running in a virtualiz on
in a virtualizer on a virtualized
environ hypervisor on one computer one
CPU but in the world of AI it's a whole
bunch of computers working
together to
generate to reason to think to answer
your query and so all of these These
computers are working together in such a
way as to respond smartly and quickly.
And meanwhile, you're not the only
customer of that cloud. So, a whole
bunch of other customers are using that
same computer. And so, notice the
difference is not only virtualizing one
computer, but it's really about sharing
a distributed high performance computing
AI supercomputer. And so, the computing
model is different. And we invented this
fabric called MVLink connected to either
Infiniban or connected to Spectrum X so
that we could scale up the computer make
it large and scale out the computer for
distributed computing. And so this
fabric is foundational to Nvidia's AI
leadership. This is how we went from
being a processor company to being a AI
infrastructure company or AI data center
company. And so this value, this
incredible
capability is m what makes makes it
possible for us to do what we do. Well,
what we decided to do was to open this
infrastructure. So you can connect to
Nvidia's scale up MVLink, scale out
Spectrum X and scale out Infiniban using
a chiptochip chiplet that we work on
together. And so whether you're you
decide to connect a CPU to that or
decide to connect a async to that,
you're you can now connect your
intellectual property, your
differentiation into our fabric. And so
whether it's whether it's from the
customer's perspective, they have the
benefit now of accessing this incredible
technology or from our perspective, our
ecosystem could be connected to
anybody's ecosystem. And so it's a
win-win for everybody. And so anyways,
that's the that's the big idea and um
everybody's so surprised that Nvidia
would open this intellectual property uh
to everybody which is a statement about
how incredibly valuable it is. This is
the fifth generation NVLink and Nvlink
is not just you know Ethernet with light
protocol. Okay, MVL MVLink is is the
ultimate computing
fabric and that's why we are very
excited because we have now really a
strong relationship to work together.
You probably don't know Jensen our
engineers really despite the challenges
and the uh I mean it's a difficult thing
to do that CPU but they really enjoy
working with your people they enjoy the
open the communication. Yeah. Yeah. It's
uh I want to say this. I mean you guys
all know that right? Because we're
really nice.
Look, you you make sure you tell your
engineers, okay? No, they're not nice.
I'm nice. I'm just No, I'm Look, here
here's the the thing is the thing that
that's really a big idea is we went from
being a computer company. What we're
doing together now is building the AI
infrastructure for the planet. Every
company will have AI factories. Of
course, you have one. Every industry
will have AI
infrastructure. There will be AI
infrastructure across the world. This is
such a gigantic initiative. And you
started you started uh building custom
AS6 and I think you by the way Mina is
incredible at collaboration. The fact of
the matter is we put these two chips
together. The fact that either chip
indivi independently works is a miracle
in itself. combining the two of them
together, you know, when you have, you
know, 10% working probability and added
to
7% mine's the 10%, yours is 7%. And you
put the two of
them. I'm just kidding. So, so anyways,
when you take two complex things and you
put them together, the likelihood of it
working is extremely small. And yet the
interface is ex right it's
state-of-the-art. Okay. And so so so the
the IP that you guys have the all of the
certis all of the design methodology
remember these two chips worked first
time these two chips work first time
built in two different companies coming
together fused together not connected
over PCI Express fused together in a
common package there's 0% chance it was
going to
work other than
you I just didn't want to say it out
loud in the beginning until it until I
was proven wrong. And so, but anyways,
the the the two engineering teams really
love working with each other because
they're so they're completely excellent.
And so, I I love the fact that you're
you're building semi semi-custom AS6 and
all these accelerators uh for the
world's hyperscalers. The the thing that
we're doing together in addition to that
is we're essentially building
semicustom AI infrastructure. Yes. And
so now at the whole data center scale,
we have a fabric, this MVLink and
Spectrum X, MVLink and Quantum, right?
Either one, whichever you you choose.
Um, but you have this MVLink fabric that
you can now plug our GPUs into, your
CPUs into, their A6 into, my CPUs in,
and we could create essentially a
semi-custom infrastructure. And then
we'll, you know, next step is just
blanket the planet with it.
Vince, hear that? That's how easy it is.
Some Let me see. Now I can uh steal at
least half of your
word. This guy is AI infrastructure guy.
Remember yesterday? I'm a construction
worker. Yeah, we're a semi
infrastructure guy.
It's so nice to have you here again,
Jensen. I truly appreciate your support
help. I love our partnership to our
company, to our people, engineers, they
love it. Thank you. And uh Thank you
very much. I've been working with Rick
since my 20s.
Really? Well, how old was I? Or how
young was I?
No, actually, it's not far off. I've
been working with with Rick since my
30s. Yeah. Yeah. My early 30s. Yeah. It
was a great memory but also great
achievement that I personally kind of
um watch and admire. Thank you. And uh
when I started working with Rick, he's
younger than I am now.
[Applause]
Well, I take that as a compliment. Okay.
So in in return for your
compliment, I have something for you.
Yes. And today
now remember
uh March GTC time you serve me with a
delicious
wonderful rich pancake with sausage from
Dennis. Remember that? Yes. I had a
That's my my specialty. Yeah. his
special. He came out in red apron with
Dennis. I don't know who he worked for,
but
Dennis
Dennis I I took a big bite. I enjoyed
it, but yeah, I didn't take the second
bite because everybody else was kind of
a just put up over there. I thought I
want to show
my composure, not not just
walloping the whole the whole thing. So
to but it's great. It's great. I do have
something for you here today. We all
know what Jensen likes the best in
Taiwan. Nine
market. One of the best other than the
business nine market, right? One of your
favorite I
think the fruit lady, a lady of an
right.
her
fresh fruits of the day today. Mhm.
No way.
I have tomato. Oh, fantastic.
I have green mango. Wow. Wow. These are
all my favorites. And I have guava. Oh
my gosh. All in the original package.
Okay, you can see. This is our Taiwan
nine market
package. No remarketing. Okay. Other
than of course the Wow. So J, I want to
offer you this. You got me all excited.
I thought I was going to get like a
bottle of fine whiskey or
something. I need to apply for that
budget.
But I think thanks for that. Hey, this
is really Thank you. Wonderful. This is
a treasure. Thank you. I didn't want you
to take pick up this picture. This is a
This is a real treasure. Hang on a
second. Let me Let me take this out.
This green mango is so good. You guys
have any Westerners here? I This is
treasure right here. This is gold.
Yeah, she's terrific. If you don't if
you don't Yeah. Go see her. Her name is
Fruit Lady.
Everybody everybody calls her fruit
lady. Now apparently she she's uh gone
on to tremendous stardom.
Yeah. Jensen in addition to enabling the
AI infrastructure big sucker but also
enabling many small
businesses like the uh brew lady
restaurants you just talked about
flowers. Flowers. He he couldn't get a
onion. Yeah. He couldn't get a
reservation because they're all
full by our local clients. Right. That's
true. And so I just dropped in without
without uh without a reservation. And
all of the customers are so nice. They
rearranged themselves so I could sit
down
and they everyone took a picture with
you. I took a picture with
everyone. That is authentic. Jensen. I
Oh, I didn't say that, but I want to say
that in public. I really appreciate.
Don't embarrass me. Yeah.
Authenticity. I mean,
authentic. When you said that word
yourself,
approachable. Everyone, well, not today.
Not now. Okay. But when you see him on
the street, take a picture.
Well, again, thank you so much. I hope
you enjoy the media tech story today.
and also enjoy Jensen here today. His
wonderful
Thank you. wonderful help to us. Thank
you. And and I want to thank MediaTek
and all your engineers, the management
team. Uh it really is you are really
genuinely a world-class company and it's
uh the technology you have uh the
collaboration spirit uh the just the can
do attitude and quite frankly the fact
that you build it right the first time.
You know, these are all things that are
that are really uh genuinely world
class. Great. We will do better. Thank
you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you,
Rick.